[
    {
        "option1": "Do you cook ?",
        "option2": "Can you do cook ?",
        "option3": "May you cook ?",
        "option4": "Can you cook ?",
        "question": "তুমি কি রান্না করতে পারো ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Can you not cook ?",
        "option2": "You can not cook ?",
        "option3": "Can not cook you ?",
        "option4": "Not can you cook ?",
        "question": "তুমি কি রান্না করতে পারো না ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Can I cook for you today ?",
        "option2": "May I cook for you today ?",
        "option3": "Can cook I for you today ?",
        "option4": "May cook I for you today ?",
        "question": "আমি কি আজ তোমার জন্য রান্না করতে পারি ?",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Jewel may cook not for you today.",
        "option2": "Jewel can not cook for you today.",
        "option3": "Jewel may not cook for you today.",
        "option4": "Jewel can cook not for you today.",
        "question": " জুয়েল আজ তোমার জন্য রান্না না-ও করতে পারে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "May Jakaria go at your house tomorrow ?",
        "option2": "Tomorrow can Jakaria go to your house ?",
        "option3": "Can Jakaria go to your house on tomorrow ?",
        "option4": "May Jakaria go to your house tomorrow ?",
        "question": " জাকারিয়া কি আগামীকাল তোমার বাড়ি যেতে পারে ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Khokon can do the work. But today he can not do that.",
        "option2": "Khokon may do the work. But he may not do that today.",
        "option3": "Khokon can do the work. But he may not do that today.",
        "option4": "Khokon may do the work. But he can not do that today.",
        "question": " খোকন কাজটা করতে সমর্থ । কিন্তু ও আজ ওটা না-ও করতে পারে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "May my son learn English from you ?",
        "option2": "Can my son learn English from you ?",
        "option3": "May my son learn English to you ?",
        "option4": "Can my son learn English to you ?",
        "question": "আমার ছেলে কি আপনার কাছে ইংরিজি শিখতে পারে ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I can Mathematics good.",
        "option2": "I can do Mathematics well.",
        "option3": "I can good in Mathematics.",
        "option4": "I can Mathematics well.",
        "question": "আমি অঙ্ক ভালো পারি",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Mijanur can walked 12 years back.",
        "option2": "Mijanur could walked back 12 years.",
        "option3": "Mijanur could walk 12 years back.",
        "option4": "Mijanur could walk back 12 years.",
        "question": "মিজানুর ১২ বছর আগে হাঁটতে পারত",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "You could go to watch the match.",
        "option2": "You can go to watch the match.",
        "option3": "You could went to watch the match.",
        "option4": "You may go to watch the match.",
        "question": "তুমি খেলাটা দেখতে যেতে পারতে",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Can you not win day before yesterday ?",
        "option2": "Could you not win day before yesterday ?",
        "option3": "Yesterday before day could you not win ?",
        "option4": "Could you not won yesterday before day ?",
        "question": "তোমরা পরশু জিততে পারলে না ?",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Nafsina can not sleep before few days. Now she can.",
        "option2": "Nafsina could not sleep before few days. Now she can.",
        "option3": "Nafsina could not sleep few days back. Now can.",
        "option4": "Nafsina could not sleep few days back. Now she can.",
        "question": "কিছুদিন আগে নাফসিনা ঘুমোতে পারত না । কিন্তু এখন পারে ।",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "I can not do this work.",
        "option2": "I am not able to doing this work.",
        "option3": "I am not being able to do this work.",
        "option4": "I am not canning to do this work.",
        "question": "আমি এই কাজটা পারছি না",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]